imagine if this actually happened to you
what if would you know what to do we do
so your family will put your kind
children's covers third party liability
damage to your car and cover your
medical expenses if you are injured but
did you know you can also claim for more
FWD insurance insurance if you reach
your destination safely we bet you
didn't know that we cover taxi cost
include salary with an accident if your
car is unsafe to drive you'll be
reimbursed a cost to your car to a
workshop you're also guaranteed one of
the best warranties against workmanship
defects when you get your car repaired
at any one of our premium workshops
personal belongings in the car can be
scratched broken or dented during
accidents will pay for your personal
items to event they're lost or damaged
so you've got places to be
no worries receive a daily transport
allowance while your car is being
repaired
it's all yours again as good as new
how is that for comprehensive coverage
there's more will ensure anyone you
trust to drive your car without even
having to inform us and if you're
current no claim discount is 50% you get
to keep it as long as you stay with FWD
insurance
[Music]